HIGHLIGHTS OF QUALIFICATIONS

Over 7 years of in-depth experience in the mobile game industry.

Led the development of products and services during a period of 7 years.

Ability to organize, prioritize and work under extreme work pressure, heavy workload, and deadlines.

Works well independently or in a team environment.

Friendly, positive, and responsible personality.

Well-organized and good at time management skills.

HYUK-JIN KWON

Software Engineer / Game Developer

PROFILE

Seeking an employment opportunity in a Software Engineering-related field. Strives to improve self-development and work-system efficiency based on sincerity and responsibility. Enjoys new challenges and in being adaptable. Adept at repetitive tasks and improving processes.

CONTACT

PHONE: 548-255-0872

ADDRESS:

356 Havendale Crescent, Waterloo, Ontario, N2T2T2

EMAIL:

wkwkdaus79@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hyuk-jinkwon-82a040231/?iohid=1234

Experience:

nttps://arrve.google.com/file/a/1qv1tsExc aSOflvgSuOPhWWwttkJhykRbV/view?us

Github:

https://github.com/hyukiin87

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Part-time

AUG 2022 - Present

Ah-So Fine Foods Inc - Kitchener, Canada

Delivery and packaging.

Game Developer

MAR 2017 - DEC 2021

Netmarble N2 – Seoul, South Korea

- Achieved high numbers of downloads, high ratings, and sales records of applications.
- Successfully developed, managed, and serviced several mobile games.
- Maintained smooth collaboration with other department members.
- Improved complex data and created related tools to improve work efficiency.

Game System Designer

JUN 2015 - MAR 2017

Entwell - Seoul, South Korea

- Had overall responsibility for game system design.
- Managed all data and design balancing.
- Ensured stable customer management and community management.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

C, C++, C#, .NET and WPF, Python, JavaScript, mySQL, ASP, PHP, Proficient in Microsoft Word and Excel, Unity

Languages: English and Korean

Certification: Computer Specialist in Spreadsheet & Database Level

Education:

Conestoga College – Waterloo, Canada SEP 2021 – APR 2023

Software Engineering Technician

Yeonsung University – Gyeonggi-do, South Korea FEB 2008 – FEB 2012 Information Communication Technology GPA: 3.92